alvarezandmarsal.com 2019-10-01

# Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions for Use of this Website | Alvarez & Marsal

**A &M Privacy Policy** 

Alvarez & Marsal Holdings, LLC ('A&M', we”, “our”, “us”) is strongly committed to complying with all applicable data protection laws and regulations within every jurisdiction in which A&M operates.

This privacy policy describes why and how we collect and use personal data and provides information about individuals’ rights.  It applies to personal data provided to us, both by individuals themselves or by others. We may use personal data provided to us for any of the purposes described in this privacy policy or as otherwise stated at the point of collection. Personal data is any information relating to an identified or identifiable living person.  A&M processes personal data for numerous purposes, and the means of collection, lawful basis of processing, use, disclosure, and retention periods for each purpose may differ.  

A&M does not process, transfer, disclose or distribute personal data other than as described in this policy without consent from individuals to do so, unless required by law or regulation. To find out more about our specific processing activities, please go to the relevant sections of this policy.

## Our Processing Activities

To find out more please go to the relevant sections of this policy. 

 **Business contacts      
A&M’s clients (and individuals associated with our clients)  
Individuals who use our applications  
Others who contact us  
Our personnel  
Recruitment applicants  
Vendors and suppliers (including subcontractors and individuals associated with our vendors and suppliers)  
Visitors to our website  
Security  
When and how we share personal data and locations of processing  
Data retention  
Terms and conditions for use of the Website ** ****

### Changes to this privacy policy

A&M regularly reviews this privacy policy and reserves the right to modify or amend it at any time.

This privacy policy was last updated in April 2019.

### Data controller and contact information

The data controller is Alvarez & Marsal Holdings, LLC, with its registration address at 600 Madison Avenue, 8th Floor, New York, New York, 10022, and other A&M affiliates as applicable (such as other A&M affiliates that are contracting parties for the purposes of providing or receiving services).  
If you have any questions about this privacy policy or how and why we process personal data, please contact us at:  
Data Protection Office  
Alvarez & Marsal Holdings, LLC  
600 Madison Avenue   
8th Floor   
New York, New York, 10022  
Email: [data.protection.office@alvarezandmarsal.com](mailto:data.protection.office@alvarezandmarsal.com)  
Phone: +1 212 759 4433

### Individuals’ rights 

You have rights in relation to the personal data we hold about you. We set out below an outline of those rights which may exist in your case and how to exercise those rights. Please note that we will require you to verify your identity before responding to any requests to exercise your rights. To exercise any of your rights, please complete the [Data Subject Access Request form](https://app-de.onetrust.com/app/#/webform/fbdc8209-661b-4756-a6fb-81292f781792). Alternatively, you can email [data.protection.office@alvarezandmarsal.com](mailto:data.protection.office@alvarezandmarsal.com). Please note that for each of the rights below we may have valid legal reasons to refuse your request. In and such instance we will let you know if that is the case. 

  *  **Access:** You have the right to know whether we process personal data about you, and if we do, to access data we hold about you, and certain information about how we use it and with whom we share it.  
  *  **Portability:** You have the right to receive a reasonable subset of the personal data you provide us if we process it on the basis of our contract with you, or with your consent. You also have the right to request that we transfer such personal data to another party. If you request we transfer the personal data to another party, please ensure you provide details of that party, and note that we can only do so where it is technically feasible. We are not responsible for the security of the personal data or its processing once received by the third party. 
  *  **Correction:** You have the right to require us to correct any personal data held about you that is inaccurate, and to have incomplete data completed. 
  *  **Erasure:** You may request that we erase the personal data we hold about you in the following circumstances:  where you believe it is no longer necessary for us to hold the personal data; we are processing the personal data on the basis of your consent and you wish to withdraw your consent; we are processing your data on the basis of our legitimate interest and you object to such processing; you no longer wish us to use your data to send you marketing material / information; or you believe we are unlawfully processing your data.  Please provide as much detail as possible on your reasons for the request to assist us in determining whether you have a valid basis for erasure. 
  *  **Restriction of Processing to Storage Only:** You have a right to restrict us from processing the personal data we hold about you, other than for storage purposes, in the following circumstances: 
    * you believe the personal data is not accurate. In such a case, for the period it takes us to verify the accuracy of the data, processing will cease, unless you consent to processing, or if processing is required for legal purposes; 
    * the processing is unlawful, but you do not want the erasure of personal data, and instead request the restriction of the use of that data; 
    * we no longer need the personal data for the purposes of processing but you require us to retain the data for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims; and 
    * you have objected to us processing personal data we hold about you on the basis of our legitimate interest and you wish us to stop processing the personal data while we determine whether there is an overriding interest in us retaining such personal data.
  *  **Objection:** You have the right to object to our processing of data about you and we will consider your request.  Please provide us with details as to your reasoning so that we can assess whether there is a compelling overriding interest in us continuing to process such data or whether we need to process it in relation to legal claims.

### Exercising your rights 

Your rights, as described above, may be exercised by completing the [Data Subject Access Request form](https://app-de.onetrust.com/app/#/webform/fbdc8209-661b-4756-a6fb-81292f781792).  Alternatively you can email us at [data.protection.office@alvarezandmarsal.com](mailto:data.protection.office@alvarezandmarsal.com). 

 **Access to personal data**    
To access personal data held by us as a data controller, please complete the [Data Subject Access Request form](https://app-de.onetrust.com/app/#/webform/fbdc8209-661b-4756-a6fb-81292f781792). Alternatively, you can email us at [data.protection.office@alvarezandmarsal.com](mailto:data.protection.office@alvarezandmarsal.com). We may charge a reasonable fee for a request for access of personal data in accordance with applicable law.  Responses to any requests for information will be provided within legally required time limits.

 **Amendment of personal data**  
To update personal data submitted to us, please complete the [Data Subject Access Request form](https://app-de.onetrust.com/app/#/webform/fbdc8209-661b-4756-a6fb-81292f781792). Alternatively, you can  email us at [data.protection.office@alvarezandmarsal.com](mailto:data.protection.office@alvarezandmarsal.com) or, where appropriate, contact us via the relevant website registration page, or by amending the personal details held on relevant applications with which you registered.

When practically possible, once we are informed that any personal data processed by us is no longer accurate, we will make corrections (where appropriate) based on your updated information.

 **Withdrawal of consent**  
Where we process personal data based on consent, you have a right to withdraw consent at any time.  We do not generally process personal data based on consent (because we can usually rely on another legal basis).  To withdraw consent to our processing of your personal data, please complete the [Data Subject Access Request form](https://app-de.onetrust.com/app/#/webform/fbdc8209-661b-4756-a6fb-81292f781792). Alternatively, you can  email us at [data.protection.office@alvarezandmarsal.com](mailto:data.protection.office@alvarezandmarsal.com) ; or, to stop receiving an email from an A&M marketing list, please click on the unsubscribe link in the relevant email received from us.  

 **Objection to Marketing  **  
At any time, you have the right to object to our processing of data about you in order to send you marketing information, including where we build profiles for such purposes, and we will stop processing the data for that purpose.

### Complaints

We hope that you won’t ever need to, but if you do want to complain about our use of personal data, please send an email with the details of your complaint to [data.protection.office@alvarezandmarsal.com](mailto:data.protection.office@alvarezandmarsal.com).  We will look into and respond to any and all complaints we receive.

You also have the right to lodge a complaint with the supervisory body of the European Union country within which you reside, work, or where the alleged infringement of your personal data protection rights took place.

## Our Processing Activities

### Business contacts

#### Collection of personal data

A&M processes personal data about contacts (existing and potential A&M clients and/or individuals associated with them) using a customer relationship management system (the “A&M CRM”).  
A&M does not sell or otherwise release personal data contained in the A&M CRM to third parties for the purpose of allowing them to market their products and services without consent from individuals to do so.

The collection of personal data about contacts and the addition of that personal data to the A&M CRM is initiated by A&M personnel and will include name, employer name, contact title, phone, email and other business contact details.   In addition, the A&M CRM may collect data from A&M email (sender name, recipient name, date and time) and calendar (organiser name, participant name, date and time of event) systems concerning interactions between A&M personnel and contacts or third parties.  

#### Use of personal data

Personal data relating to business contacts may be processed by A&M personnel to learn more about an account, client or opportunity they have an interest in, for the following purposes:

  * Administering, managing and developing our businesses and services;
  * Providing information about us and our range of services;
  * Making contact information available to other A&M personnel;
  * Identifying clients/contacts with similar needs;
  * Describing the nature of a contact’s relationship with A&M; and
  * Performing analytics, including producing metrics for A&M leadership, such as on trends, relationship maps, sales intelligence and progress against account business goals

In addition, the A&M CRM evaluates the strength of interactions between an A&M user and a contact.  This ranking is primarily based on interaction frequency, duration, how recent the contact was and response time.   

### A&M’s clients (and individuals associated with our clients)

#### Collection of personal data

Where we need to process personal data to provide professional services, our clients are responsible for providing the necessary information to the data subjects regarding its use.  This includes, where a client engagement involves the transfer of personal data outside the European Union, that the relevant clients are responsible (where required) for providing appropriate notice to or obtaining appropriate consent from, the individuals whose data may be transferred. 

Our clients may use relevant sections of this privacy policy or refer data subjects to this privacy policy if they consider it appropriate to do so.

Given the diversity of the services we provide to clients, we process many categories of personal data, including:

  * Contact details;
  * Business activities;
  * Information about management and employees;
  * Payroll and other financial-related details; and
  * Investments and other financial interests.

#### Use of personal data

We use personal data for the following purposes:

  * Providing professional services. Our services often require us to process personal data in order to provide advice and deliverables;
  * Administering, managing and developing our businesses and services;
  * In order to operate our business, including:
    * managing our relationship with clients;
    * developing our businesses and services;
    * maintaining and using IT systems;
    * hosting or facilitating the hosting of events; and
  * Personal data may be processed as part of the security monitoring that we undertake; for example, automated scans to identify harmful emails.  We have security measures in place to protect our and our clients’ information (including personal data), which involve detecting, investigating and resolving security threat;
  * We monitor the services provided to clients for quality purposes, which may involve processing personal data stored on the relevant client file;  
  * We collect and hold personal data as part of our client engagement and acceptance procedures.  As part of those procedures we carry out searches using publicly available sources (such as internet searches and sanctions lists) to identify politically exposed persons and heightened risk individuals and organisations and check that there are no issues that would prevent us from working with a particular client;  
  * Unless we are asked not to, we use client business contact details to provide information that we think will be of interest about us and our services.  Examples include industry updates and insights, information on other services that may be relevant, and invitations to events; and   
  * As a professional services firm, we and our personnel are subject to legal, regulatory and professional obligations.  We maintain certain records to demonstrate that our services are provided in compliance with those obligations and those records may contain personal data.

### Individuals who use our applications

We provide external users with access to various applications used by A&M.  Such applications will contain their own privacy statements explaining why and how personal data is collected and processed by those applications.  

### Others who contact us

We collect personal data when an individual gets in touch with us with a question, comment or feedback (such as name, contact details and contents of the communication).  In these cases, we will only use the data for the purpose of responding to the communication.

### Our personnel

We collect personal data concerning our own employees, partners, managers, directors, officers and agents as part of the administration, management and operation of our business activities.

### Recruitment applicants

When applying for a role at A&M, applicants should refer to the information made available for details about why and how personal data is collected and processed.    
For more detail about our recruitment processes, please go to our Recruitment Policy.

### Vendors and suppliers (including subcontractors and individuals associated with our vendors and suppliers)

#### Collection of personal data

We collect and process personal data about our vendors and suppliers (including subcontractors and individuals associated with them) in order to manage the relationship, enter into a contract, receive services from our suppliers and, where relevant, provide professional services to our clients.

#### Use of personal data

We use personal data for the following purposes:

  * We process personal data in relation to our suppliers and their personnel as necessary to receive the services; 
  * Where a supplier is helping us to deliver professional services to our clients, we process personal data about the individuals involved in providing the services in order to administer and manage our relationship with the supplier and the relevant individuals (for example, where our supplier is working with us as part of an A&M team providing professional services to our clients);
  * In order to operate our business, including:
    * managing our relationship with suppliers;
    * developing our businesses and services;
    * maintaining and using IT systems;
    * hosting or facilitating the hosting of events; and
    * administering and managing our website and systems and applications;
  * Personal data may be processed as part of the security monitoring that we undertake; for example, automated scans to identify harmful emails.    We have security measures in place to protect our and our clients’ information (including personal data), which involve detecting, investigating and resolving security threats; 
  * We collect and hold personal data as part of our supplier contracting procedures.  We monitor the services provided for quality purposes, which may involve processing personal data;
  * Unless we are asked not to, we use business contact details to provide information that we think will be of interest about us and our services.  Examples include industry updates and insights, information on other services that may be relevant, and invitations to events;
  * As a professional services firm, we and our personnel are subject to legal, regulatory and professional obligations.  We maintain certain records to demonstrate that our services are provided in compliance with those obligations and those records may contain personal data.

### Visitors to our website

#### Collection of personal data

Visitors to our websites are generally in control of the personal data shared with us.  We may capture limited personal data automatically via the use of cookies on our website.  Please see the section on ‘cookies’ below for more information.

We receive personal data, such as name, title, company address, email address, and telephone  numbers, from website visitors; for example, when an individual subscribes to updates from us.  
Visitors are also able to send an email to us through the website. Their messages will contain the user’s name and email address, as well as any additional information the user may wish to include in the message.

We ask that you do not provide sensitive information (such as race or ethnic origin; political opinions; religious or philosophical beliefs; trade union membership; physical or mental health; genetic data; biometric data; sexual life or sexual orientation; and criminal records) to us when using our website.

#### Cookies and website navigational information

We use small text files called ‘cookies’ which are placed on your hard drives to assist in personalising and enriching your browsing experience by displaying content that is more likely to be relevant and of interest to you. The use of cookies is now standard operating procedure for most websites.  However, if you are uncomfortable with the use of cookies, most browsers now permit users to opt-out of receiving them. You need to accept cookies in order register on our website.  You may find other functionality in the website impaired if you disable cookies. After termination of the visit to our site, you can always delete the cookie from your system if you wish.  Please see the sections below for further details.

#### Website navigational information

As you navigate through our websites, we automatically collect technical information including Internet Protocol (“IP”) addresses through Web server logs, and other information through 'cookies' and Web beacons.   
 **An IP Address** is a number that identifies your computer or other device whenever you access the Internet, allowing computers and servers to recognize and communicate with each other over a network. A&M collects technical information, including the IP address used to connect your computer to the Internet, your login information, browser type and version, time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform; to aggregate non-personal information for analysis and trending.      
 **A Uniform Resource Locator (‘URL’)** is the address of a specific website or file on the Internet. We collect information about your visit, including the full URL clickstream to, through and from our site (including date and time); items you viewed or searched for; page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page; and any phone number used to call our customer service number.     
 **Cookies** are small text files placed on your hard drive that allow the site to remember who you are. As an example, A&M uses cookies to compile aggregate statistics to enhance the overall website experience.   
On our web site, a notification ‘cookie’ banner will appear requiring your explicit consent to place and collect cookies. If you do not provide consent, target/advertising cookies will not be placed on your browser and your computer will not be identified.  When you accept, your selection will be valid for a period of one year. Performance and Functionality cookies may still be required for necessary operation of our site. Such cookies will not be blocked through the use of this notification banner. If you wish to revoke your selection, you may do so by clearing your browser's cookies (often found in your browser's Tools or Preferences menu).

Read more about how A&M uses cookies in our Cookies Policy: [https://www.alvarezandmarsal.com/cookie-policy.](https://www.alvarezandmarsal.com/cookie-policy)

 **Web Beacons** are small image files on a Web page that may be used, for example, to count users that have accessed a page, or to gather other related website statistics. By disabling browser cookies, unique information associated with web beacons will also be disabled.

#### Use of personal data

When a visitor provides personal data to us, we will use it for the purposes for which it was provided to us as stated at the point of collection (or as obvious from the context of the collection).    
Typically, personal data is collected to:

  * register for certain areas of the site;
  * subscribe to updates;  
  * enquire for further information;
  * distribute requested reference materials;
  * submit bios / curriculum vitae (CVs);
  * monitor and enforce compliance with our terms and conditions for use of our website;
  * administer and manage our website, including confirming and authenticating identity and preventing unauthorised access to restricted areas, premium content or other services limited to registered users; and
  * aggregate data for website analytics and improvements.

Unless we are asked not to, we may also use your data to contact you with information about A&M’s business, services and events, and other information which may be of interest to you.  Should visitors subsequently choose to unsubscribe from mailing lists or any registrations, we will provide instructions on the appropriate webpage, in our communication to the individual, or the individual may contact us by email to [data.protection.office@alvarezandmarsal.com](mailto:data.protection.office@alvarezandmarsal.com).

Our websites do not collect or compile personal data for the dissemination or sale to outside parties for consumer marketing purposes, or host mailings on behalf of third parties.  If there is an instance where such information may be shared with a party that is not an A&M affiliate, the visitor will be asked for their consent beforehand.

#### Links to other sites

A&M’s website may contain links to other sites that are not governed by this privacy policy but by other privacy statements that may be different. We recommend that users review the privacy policy of each website visited before disclosing any personal data.

#### Public forums (bulletin boards, blogs, chat rooms, etc.)

A&M may provide links to social media platforms maintained on separate servers by individuals or organizations over which A&M has no control. A&M makes no representations or warranties regarding the accuracy of information located on such servers. In addition, A&M cannot be held responsible if you share Personal Data on social media platforms that is subsequently used, misused or otherwise appropriated by another user. We recommend reviewing the privacy policy of any third-party site that may be linked from our website to determine their use of your Personal Data.

## Security

We take the security of all the data we hold very seriously.  We have a framework of policies, procedures and training in place covering data protection, confidentiality and security. We regularly review the appropriateness of the measures we have in place to keep the data we hold secure.  Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorized access.

## 

We will only share personal data with others when we are legally permitted to do so.  When we share data with others, we put contractual arrangements and security mechanisms in place to protect the data and to comply with our data protection, confidentiality and security standards.

We are a global professional services firm and sometimes use third parties located in other countries to assist us with business activities.   As a result, personal data may be transferred outside the countries where our clients are located.  This includes countries outside the European Union ("EU") and to countries that do not have laws that provide specific protection for personal data.   We have taken steps to ensure all personal data is provided adequate protection, and that all transfers of personal data outside the EU and United Kingdom (“UK”) are done lawfully.  When we transfer personal data outside of the EU and UK to a country not determined by the European Commission as providing an adequate level of protection for personal data, the transfers will be under an agreement which covers the EU requirements for the transfer of personal data outside the EU (such as the European Commission approved standard contractual clauses).

In addition, one subsidiary of A&M, Alvarez & Marsal Disputes and Investigations, LLC, is certified under the EU-U.S. and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Frameworks as set forth by the [U.S. Department of Commerce](https://www.privacyshield.gov/welcome) regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information that is transferred from the EU, Switzerland or UK to that entity, within the scope of its certification.  Further details can be found here.

Personal data held by us may be transferred to:

#### Other A&M affiliate entities

For details of A&M’s locations, please click here. We may share personal data with other A&M affiliates where necessary for administrative purposes and to provide professional services to our clients (e.g. when providing services involving advice from A&M affiliates in different territories).  Our business contacts are visible to and used by A&M personnel from A&M affiliates to learn more about a contact, client or opportunity they have an interest in (please see the Business Contacts section of this privacy policy for more information about our processing of this type of data).

#### Third party organisations that provide applications / functionality, data processing or IT services to us

We use third parties to support us in providing our services and to help provide, run and manage our internal information technology (IT) systems.  Examples include providers of IT, cloud based “software as a service”, identity management, website hosting and management, data analysis, data back-up, security and storage services.  The servers powering and facilitating cloud infrastructure are located in secure data centres around the world, and personal data may be stored in any one of them.

#### Third party organisations or advisers that otherwise assist us in our operations

We use third parties to assist us in our operations, e.g. auditors and other professional advisers.  

#### Law enforcement or other government and regulatory agencies or to other third parties as required by, and in accordance with, applicable law or regulation

Occasionally, we may receive requests from third parties with authority to obtain disclosure of personal data. Examples may include checking that we are complying with applicable law and regulation; or to investigate an alleged crime, or establish, exercise or defend legal rights.  We will only fulfil requests for personal data in accordance with applicable law or regulation.

We will also disclose personal data where reasonably necessary to:

  * enforce our terms and conditions and other agreements, including investigation of any potential violation thereof;
  * detect, prevent or otherwise address security, fraud or technical issues; 
  * protect the rights, property or safety of us, our personnel, a third party or the public as required or permitted by law (exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection); or 
  * in the event that we sell any business or assets, in which case we will disclose your data to the prospective buyer of such business or assets;

#### Data retention

We retain the personal data processed by us in accordance with our policies or otherwise for as long as is considered necessary for the purpose for which it was collected (including as required by applicable law or regulation).   Personal data may be held for longer periods where extended retention periods are required in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights.  
_____________________________________________________________________________________________

## Terms and conditions for use of the Website

WELCOME TO THE ALVAREZ & MARSAL ("A&M") WEB SITE (THE "SITE"), A PROPERTY OF ALVAREZ & MARSAL HOLDINGS, LLC (“A&M HOLDINGS”). PLEASE READ THE FOLLOWING TERMS AND CONDITIONS BEFORE USING THIS SITE. If you do not agree or cannot comply with these Terms and Conditions, please do not access or otherwise use this Site. By using this Site, you signify your agreement to these Terms and Conditions and agree to be bound by the same.

### About A&M Holdings

A&M Holdings is the parent company of various global professional services companies.  References to A&M and Alvarez & Marsal in this statement are to A&M Holdings and its subsidiaries (each, an “A&M Entity”).  The content on this site is owned and operated by A&M Holdings which serves in a coordinating role for the purpose of maintaining this site but does not provide services to A&M clients.  Each A&M Entity is a separate and distinct legal entity responsible for its own conduct.  Except as otherwise may be expressly set forth in a written agreement between you and such A&M Entity, in no event will A&M Holdings or any other A&M Entity take responsibility or be liable for the conduct of another A&M Entity.

These are  the current Terms and Conditions for use of this Site which may change without giving notice to you individually. Should A&M materially modify these Terms and Conditions, A&M will post a formal notice on its Site home page for thirty (30) days from the date such change is implemented.

### Acceptable Use

We may restrict your access or revoke your right to use this Site without giving you notice. You may only use this Site for lawful purposes and may not disrupt, modify or interfere with this Site, any associated software, hardware or servers or any use of this Site by third parties. Please check to make sure that your use of this Site complies with all applicable local, state and federal laws.

Any textual or graphic materials you copy, print, or download is licensed to you by A&M for your personal use only. Scraping is strictly prohibited. Under no circumstances may you modify any of the textual or graphic materials found on this Site or create derivative works therefrom. Should you fail to comply with any provision of these Terms and Conditions, this limited license will automatically terminate.

### Hyperlinks

We are not responsible for, and do not endorse the contents or information provided on any hyperlinked Sites operated by unaffiliated third parties which may be provided to you for your reference. By using this Site to link to another site, you understand that you may not make any claim against A&M or any damages or losses caused by said linking.

You may not link your Site to any internal page on this site without the express written consent of A&M. Permission is granted to only link your Site to the A&M home page located at [ **https://www.alvarezandmarsal.com**](https://www.alvarezandmarsal.com/). Additionally, you may not frame any information located on this Site on another site without the express written consent of A&M. Such consent may be requested by sending an email request to [ **Linda** **Orton**](mailto:globalmarketing@alvarezandmarsal.com?subject=Alvarez%20%26%20Marsal%20Website%20-%20Terms%20of%20Use). The permission granted herein to link to the A&M home page may also be revoked at any time without cause. Further, you may not link any Site that (i) violates any law or regulation; (ii) infringes the patent, copyright, trademark, trade secret or other intellectual property rights of others or violates any privacy, publicity or personal rights of others; or (iii) contains defamatory, obscene, threatening, abusive or hateful information or expressions.

### Intellectual Property

ALVAREZ & MARSAL, ALVAREZ & MARSAL logos and A&M are service marks of A&M. Other trademarks appearing on this Site are the property of their respective owners. Use of any trademarks owned by A&M or use of A&M's marks as metatags is strictly prohibited without A&M's express written permission.

The aggregated and individual contents of this Site including, without limitation, text, photographs, graphic images and other materials (the "Works") are protected under US and foreign copyright law. You have no right or license to reproduce, copy, edit, publish or transmit the Works except as set forth below without our express written permission.

A&M does not grant you any express or implied right under any of its trademarks, copyrights or any other proprietary information appearing on the Site. In the event that you are granted any permission to use A&M's trademarks or copyrights, you acknowledge that you will not gain any ownership rights to the same.

### Disclaimers

You are using this Site at your own risk. A&M has no duty or policy to update any information or statements contained on this Site and, therefore, such information or statements should not be relied upon as being current as of the date you access this Site. Changes may be made without notice to the graphic and textual materials available on this Site and/or the services offered by A&M described therein. The materials available on this Site may also include technical inaccuracies or typographical errors.

A&M does not guarantee that any personal information submitted will remain private (see the Privacy Policy associated with this site). A&M does not promise you that there will be no errors transmitting information to and from this Site. Additionally, A&M does not promise that information you receive from this Site is accurate or reliable or that this Site is free of computer viruses or other harmful mechanisms.

You agree to waive any claims you may have against us for any damages that you may incur as a result of using this Site. A&M may, however, make claims against you for use of this Site that violates our policies as posted on this Site. In addition, you agree to indemnify us for any claims brought against us for damages that result from your use of this Site or violations of our Terms and Conditions as posted by A&M on this Site. This Site is controlled by A&M from its offices within the State of New York, United States of America. A&M makes no representation or warranty that the materials in this Site are appropriate or available for use in any locations outside of the United States. Those who choose to access this Site from other locations do so on their own initiative and are responsible for compliance with local laws, if and to the extent local laws are applicable. Any claims regarding this Site will be governed under New York law and may only be brought in the Federal or state courts located in the State of New York. Therefore, by accepting these Terms and Conditions, you are agreeing to submit to the jurisdiction of such courts for any claims arising out of your use of this Site.

The content on this Site does not form any part of a subsequent contract entered into with any party purchasing products or services from A&M.

THIS SITE AND MATERIALS ARE PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS" BASIS, FREE OF CHARGE, WITHOUT ANY WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED. A&M, TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, DISCLAIMS ALL REPRESENTATIONS AND WARRANTIES, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED. IF YOUR USE OF THE SITE OR THE MATERIALS THEREIN RESULTS IN THE NEED FOR SERVICING OR REPLACING EQUIPMENT OR DATA, A&M IS NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR THOSE COSTS.

A&M DOES NOT WARRANT THE ACCURACY, RELIABILITY, COMPLETENESS OR USEFULNESS OF ANY INFORMATION CONTAINED ON THIS FREE SITE. A&M DOES NOT WARRANT THAT THE FUNCTIONS CONTAINED IN THE MATERIALS AVAILABLE ON THIS SITE WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR-FREE, THAT DEFECTS WILL BE CORRECTED, OR THAT THE MATERIALS, THIS SITE OR THE SERVER THAT MAKES THEM AVAILABLE ARE FREE OF VIRUSES OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS. YOU (AND NOT A&M) ASSUME THE ENTIRE COST OF ALL NECESSARY SERVICING, REPAIR AND CORRECTION.

### Disclaimer of Consequential Damages

IN NO EVENT SHALL A&M, ITS SUPPLIERS, OR ANY THIRD PARTIES MENTIONED ON THIS SITE BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES WHATSOEVER (INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, INCIDENTAL AND CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, LOST PROFITS, OR DAMAGES RESULTING FROM LOST DATA OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) RESULTING FROM THE USE OR INABILITY TO USE THIS SITE AND THE MATERIAL, WHETHER BASED ON WARRANTY, CONTRACT, TORT, OR ANY OTHER LEGAL THEORY, AND WHETHER OR NOT A&M IS ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.

### Privacy Policy

Our Privacy Policy is incorporated into these terms and conditions. 

### Entire Agreement

These Terms and Conditions constitute the entire agreement between you and A&M relating to access and use of this Site and supersede any prior or contemporaneous representations or agreements. Any rights not specifically granted by these Terms and Conditions are reserved by A&M.

 **Return to Top**
